A Guide to the Warren Morton Washington Papers WW2008.001
National Center for Atmospheric Science Library Special Collections
- Diversity Activites, 1963 - Present; 4.0 linear ft. (1 box) Box 4, Black Environmental Science Trustr (BEST) - 9 folders Box 16, Amercian Academy for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - 12 folders Box 35 UCAR/NCAR Correnspondence - 8 folders, 1 blue binder; Warren M. Washington, Ph.D., Senior Scie
  - Black Environmental Science Trust (BEST), 1986 - 1999; BEST; Folder 1 - Proposal from UCAR to NSF Folder 2 - Proposal from UCAR to NSF, cont'd Folder 3 - Correspondence (1) Folder 4 - Correspondence (2) Folder 5 - Correspondence (3) Folder 6 - Organization Folder 7 - Plan of Action Folder 8 - Pl
    - Meeting itineraries; Simpson, Michele, Washington, Warren (n. d.), Correspondence (1) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - BEST Mission/Overview/Rationale and Need, Correspondence (1) (Box 4, Folder 3)
      National Center for Atmospheric Research; African Americans - Science; Black Environmental Science Trust (BEST)
    - Possible Programs; (n.d.), Correspondence (1); Handwritten Notes (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Important Facts; Schmidt, Cynthia E.; 10/09/1990, Correspondence (1) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Bylaws of National Association of Black Environmentalists, Williams, Madeline; 10/12/1995, Correspondence (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence National Wildlife Federation; Gordon, Rue, E.; 7/1995, Correspondence (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence Michigan State University; Rice, Jane; 6/22/1995, Correspondence (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Notes Washington, Warren; 11/10/1994, Correspondence (2); Handwritten Notes (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence Yates, Albert; 10/24/1994, Correspondence (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Article Science "Bring Science Back to the Neighborhood", "Finding-and keeping-Minority Professors", "Plenty of Jobs, Little Minority Support in Biotech" (vol. 262; 11/12/1993); Williams, Madeline; 10/26/1994, Correspondence (2); Can be retrieved by paid subscription through AAAS (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence re: advisory board - BEST; Davis, Jeannie; Early, Norm; Moore, Verneeda; Persons, Waverly; Tanner, Gloria 10/11/1994, Correspondence (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence Koninic, Lewis; 10/27/1994, Correspondence (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence; Tanner, Gloria; 10/26/1994, Correspondence (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Environmental Information Networks, Inc.; "Global Warming Network Online Today"; 10/28/1994, Correspondence (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence Lynch, Debbie; Aurora Public Schools; National Association of Black Environmentalist (NABE); 10/10/1994, Correspondence (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Webb, Wellington (Mayor of City of Denver); (n.d.), Correspondence (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Drafts of Publications (n.d.), Correspondence (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Best Information Packet; Paving the way to a brighter Environmental future (n.d.), WW006; Correspondence (2)
    - Correspondence Bennett, Jeffrey O.; 9/14/1994;New York Times article "To Raise the Performance of Minorities, A College Increased its Standards"; 6/29/1994, Correspondence (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - VITA of Washington, Warren M.; 9/1994, Correspondence (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence Austin, Meg; 4/04/1994, Correspondence (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence Austin, Meg, Greenfield, Dick; 4/03/1994, Correspondence (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence Committee for the National Institute for the Environment; Hubbell, Stephen P.;11/07/1993, Correspondence (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence; Ebierly, Gene; 1/10/1994, Correspondence (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - BEST File List; 8/24/1993, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence Simpson, Michele; Mozetta Allen Fund; 9/04/1992, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Cole, Thomas; Clark Atlanta University; 4/16/1993, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Draft of Project summary Earth System Sciences Clark Atlanta University; 4/15/1993, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Brochure "Series VI: On diversity in Teaching and Learning, Dialogue on Diversity in the Classroom"; Jacobs, Janet; Simpson, Michele; (n.d.), Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence US Department of Agriculture; Natural Resources and Environmental Management (NREM); DeBree, James; Vance; John A.; 4/14/1993, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Graves, Denise; Simpson, Michele; 4/21/1993, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Barker, Harriet, Bonner, Bill; 4/13/1993, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Bonner, Bill; Einaudi, Franco; 3/29/1993; Reply Washington, Warren; 4/05/1993, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - "1993 Blacks in Science Calendar"; photocopy of check; 12/08/1992, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Article Colorado Daily; "Earth Matters: Minorities Seeing Red Instead of Green: People of color Fight Exclusion, Classism; Simpson, Michele; 2/23/1993, Correspondence(3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Comedy, Edna R.; Williamson, Sam; 3/08/1992 re: "Augmentation to UCAR's Summer Employment Program"; NCAR; 3/13/1992, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Cole, Thomas; MOU, NOAA and Department of Commerce: 3/03/1993, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Howard, Holly; 2/01/1993, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Women's Cancer Agenda; BEST; 11/13, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence American Meteorological Society; Hallgren, Richard E.; 10/26/1992, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Shaiyen, Hubert; Access Africa International, Inc.; 10/01/1992; Conference "Protecting Africa's Environment: Stiking a Balance Between the Environment and Development"; 10/29/1992, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Simpson, Michele; Boston Globe; Grossfield, Stan; 8/23/1992, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Bierly, Eugene; 5/06/1992; Article New York Times; 4/21/1992; "As Black PhD's Taper Off, Aid for Foreigners Is Assailed"; Article Daily Camera article; 5/02/1992 "Point of View: Washington Post, On the Shortage of Black Doctoral Candidates", Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Russell, Avery B.; Carnegie Corporation of New York; 1/31/1992, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Massey, Walter E.; National Science Foundation; 12/09/1991, Correspondence (3); Handwritten Notes; Working Document Attached (Box 4, Folder 5)
      National Center for Atmospheric Research; National Science Foundation
    - Correspondence Simpson, Michele; 9/23/1991-11/06/1991, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Lester, William A.; University of California, College of Chemistry; 9/27/1991, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Simpson, Michele; 8/24/1991-9/04/1991, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Notice of meeting National Advisory Committee for the National People of Color Environmental Leadership Summit 9/17/1991; 7/24/1991, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Simpson, Michele; 6/10/1991-8/05/1991, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Anderson, Charles; First National People of Color Environmental Leadership Summit; 10/24-27/1991; 7/16/1991and 6/20/1991, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Streep, Meryl; BEST; 7/12/1991, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Simpson, Michele; 6/19/1991-7/22/1991, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Black Environmental Science Trust (BEST): A Plan of Action; Draft 4/10/1991, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Jerome, Fred; Scientists' Institutive for Public Information (SIPI); Media Outreach Program co-sponsored by BEST and SIPI; 3/11/1991, Correspondence (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - BEST Stationery and Envelopes, Organization (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Articles of Incorporation: BEST, Organization (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - BEST; Mission, Overview/Rationale and Need, Background; Proposal; Project Administration; (n.d.), Organization; Ten Copies (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Organization (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Minutes Board of Directors BEST; 4/03/1995, Organization (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - BEST Agenda (n.d.), Organization; Handwritten Notes (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Certificate of Assumed or Trade Name for “BEST”; 10/04/1994, Organization (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Internal Revenue Service; Recognition and Exemption from Federal Income Tax; 5/06/1991, Organization (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Organization (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence Simpson, Michele; 2/28/1992, Organization; Handwritten Notes (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence Fairfax, Jean E.; 3/15/1990, Organization (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Organization (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence Davis, Jeannie; Franklin; Les; Moore, Verneeda; Persons, Waverly; (n.d.), Organization (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence Samuels, Claudia; Joint proposal by BEST and SIPI; 5/21/1991, Plan of Action (1) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Working draft of Black Environmental Science Trust (BEST): A Plan of Action; Simpson, Michele; Washington, Warren; 4/03/1991, Plan of Action (1); Handwritten Notes (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - BEST “A Plan of Action” draft; (n.d.), Plan of Action (1) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Notes on lay-out of “A Plan of Action”; (n.d.), Plan of Action (1) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - A Plan of Action: notes for introduction; section 1; (n.d.), Plan of Action (1); Handwritten Notes (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - A Plan of Action; notes for section 2: ‘What is BEST’; (n.d.), Plan of Action (1); Handwritten Notes (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - A Plan of Action; Background and important facts; (n.d.), Plan of Action (1); Handwritten Notes (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence Simpson, Michele; 3/13/1991, Plan of Action (1) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence Simpson, Michele; 3/21/1991, Plan of Action (1) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence Schmidt, Cynthia E.; 3/18, Plan of Action (1) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence Simpson, Michele; Grant Guidelines and Application Procedures for The Surdna Foundation June 1990; 3/27/1991, Plan of Action (1) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Article Wall Street Journal Simpson, Michele; 3/27/1991, Plan of Action (1) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Editorials Physics Today "APS Aird to Women and Minorities" (May, 1990 page 93); March, 1991, Plan of Action (1) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence Jerome, Fred; SIPI; 3/20/1991, Plan of Action (1) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - A Plan of Action; ‘What is our next step?’; (n.d.), Plan of action (1); Handwritten Notes (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Article The Oregon Stater; "Global Warming Expert Hopes to Encourage Others"; 12/1990, Plan of Action (1) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The Energy Foundation: Toward a Sustainable Energy Future; Programs and Guidelines; (n.d.), Plan of Action (1); Handwritten Notes (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The Energy Foundation: Toward a Sustainable Energy future; Energy: From Crisis to Solution; (n.d.), Plan of Action (1); Handwritten Notes (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - BEST Mission, Overview/Rationale and Need, Background Strategy, Structure, Endorsements, Conclusion; (n.d.), Plan of Action (1) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Black Environmental Science Trust; Mission, Important Facts; (n.d.), Plan of Action (2); Two Copies (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence Golden, William T.; 7/23/1990, Plan of Action (2) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence Modahl, Ann; BEST document; 4/16/1990, Plan of Action (2)
    - Correspondence Simpson, Michele; Modahl, Ann; 3/27/1990, Plan of Action (2) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence Schmidt, David; 3/20/1990, Plan of Action (2) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Font Tables for LNOS for review from Modahl, Ann for BEST document; 4/05/1990, Plan of Action (2); Handwritten Notes (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Samples of typeface for text; Modahl, Ann; Simpson, Michele; 4/2/1990, Plan of Action (2) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Draft of BEST document "original"; (n.d.), Plan of Action (2) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Draft of BEST document; Mission, Overview/Rationale and Need, Background, Strategy, Structure, Endorsements, Conclusion, Plan of Action (2) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence Schmidt, David; Modahl, Ann; 2/22/1990, Plan of Action (2) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence Simpson, Michele; Modahl, Ann; 3/30/1990, Plan of Action (2) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Draft of BEST document; Simpson, Michele; (n.d.), Plan of Action (2); Handwritten Notes (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - The Piton Foundation Annual Report 1986 and 1987; Simpson Michele; Program Officer, BEST: Press Clippings (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Boulder Technology Incubator:Introduction; Benefits and Services, Update, Client ees, Brochure; (n.d.), BEST: Press Clippings (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Article Emerge "Political Agenda: Prospects for Poison Targeted"; 10/1990, BEST: Press Clippings (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Article The Scientist "Minority Scientists Broaden Efforts to fight Environmental Woes of Poor" (Vol. 5, No. 9); 4/29/1991, BEST: Press Clippings; Four copies (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Original article from The Scientist "Minority Scientists Broaden Efforts to fight Environmental Woes of Poor" (Vol. 5, No. 9); 4/29/1991, BEST: Press Clippings (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Penn State Distinguished Awards 1991; Washington, Warren M., BEST: Press Clippings (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - The Environmental Career Organization; Connections, Spring 1992; ECO National Minority Environmental Career Conference; March, 1992, BEST: Press Clippings (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - National Action Council for Minorities in Engineering, inc; Campbell, George, Jr.; Research Letter (Vol. 3, No. 1); May, 1992, BEST: Press Clippings (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Article Sunday Camera: Today, "NCAR Climatologist takes action: forms foundation to increase number of black scientists"; 8/25/1990, BEST: Press Clippings (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - National Association of Black Environmentalists, NABE Examiner; Vo. II; 4/03/1995, BEST: Press Clippings (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Article The Scientist "Environmental Activists Recruiting Minority Scientists"; 4/29/1991, BEST: Press Clippings (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 1966 - 1980, AAAS; 16.0 linear ft. (1 box) Folder 1 - Committee on Minorities in Science General Correspondence (1 - 3)) Folder 2 - Committee on Opportunities in Science Folder 3 - Committee on Opportunities in Science Meeting Nov 17-18, 1974 Folder 4 - Committee on Opportunities in Science Meeting Nov 17-18, 1974 cont'd Folder 5 - Committee on Opportunities in Science meeting; 2/23-24/1974 Folder 6 - Committee On Opportunity in Science: Correspondence 1976 Folder 7 - Booklets Folder 8 - Committee On Opportunity in Science: Correspondence 1977 Folder 9 - Folder 10 - Folder 11 - Minority Caucus 1977 Folder 12 - (Box 16, Folder 1 - 12)
    - Correspondence Brown, Janet; 12/02/1975, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Posner, Susan E.; Conference of Minority Women Scientists; 11/07/1975, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Hall, P. Quick; 12/08/1975, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence NSF Public forum on Science for Citizens Program; 11/19/1975, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Posner, Susan; AAAS-Znaniye Distinguished Scientists Exchange Program; 10/15/1973, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Posner, Susan; 1/23/1994, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Bevan, William; 1/24/1974, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Morgan, Bryan; 1/16/1973; Correspondence Reed, Robert; Roberts, Walter Orr; UCAR; 1/02/1973, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Warren M. Washington, Ph.D., Senior Scientist -- Archives
    - Correspondence Bauer, Jim; Article The Physics Teacher "A Physics Oriented College Motivation Program for Minority Students"; Baur, James F.; Chappell, Willard R.; (Vol. 10, No. 4, April, 1972), Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Abelson, Philip H.; Wilburn, Adolph Y.; 6/26/1972-8/04/1972, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Bevan, William; 7/25/1972, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Roberts, Walter Orr; 7/17/1972, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Trumbull, Richard; AAAS Symposium on Women and Ethnic Minorities in Science and Technology: the Role of Professional Societies; 6/30/1972, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Bevan, William; 6/09/1972, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Wilburn, Adolph, Y.; 5/26/1972, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Bevan, William; Office for Minorities in Science; 5/08/1972, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Potter, David, D.; Agenda suggestions Committee on minorities of Science; 5/03/1972, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Roberts, Walter Orr; UCAR; Phillips, Norma A.; Department of Meteorology, Massachusetts Institute of Technology; 5/01/1972, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Reed, Robert J.; American Meteorological Society; 4/17/1972, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Anderson, Charles E.; AMS Program; 3/21/1972, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Potter, David D.; re: comments on Meeting Minutes; 3/13/1972, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Hamilton, Harry; College visits; 1/31/1972, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Wilburn, Adolph Y.; Joint Symposium of AAAS Committee on Minorities in Science and Section on Chemistry; 2/15/1972, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Benton, Edward; University of Colorado; 12/09/1971, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Varma, M. M.; Howard University, School of Engineering; 12/13/1971, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (1) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Phillips, Norman re: promoting opportunities for Black students; 9/17/1971-4/04/1972, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (2) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (2) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Cressman, George P.; summer employment; 10/19/1971, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (2) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Potter, Dave; Report on the Status of women in the Faculty of Arts and Sciences at Harvard; 8/10/1971, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (2) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Bevan, William; travel insurance policy; 7/07/1971, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (2) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence West, Earle H.; Journal of Negro Education; 12/01/1970, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (2) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Seeger, Raymond, J.; preliminary program for the AAAS Symposium on Contributions of Minority Groups to the Development of Science; 8/27/1970, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (2) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - List of American Indians in the Anthropology discipline (n.d.), Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (2) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence re: recruitment of members for AAAS Committee on Minorities and Science; 5/16/1970-10/19/1970, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (2) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Seeger, Raymond, J.; Chair the round-table discussion on the Contributions of the US Minority Groups to the Development of Science; 9/01/1970, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (2) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Washington, Warren; Names of potential members for the committee on Minority Representation in Science; 3/08/1970, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (2) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence re: Committee of Young Scientists; AAAS Council; Chairman of the Youth Council; 7/27/1970-8/07/1970, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (2) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Youth Advisory Council; Selected comments, summaries; 6/20/1970, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (2) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - AAAS Handbook, 1975, Committee on Minorities in Science: General Correspondence (3) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Report to AAAS Board of Directors; 1976-77, Committee on Opportunities in Science; Two Copies (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - AAAS Board of Directors; 1977, Committee on Opportunities in Science (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence Washington, Warren; 6/13/1977, Committee on Opportunities in Science; Handwritten Notes (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Scientific Engineering Technical: Manpower Comments; Vol. 11, No. 10; 11/1974, Committee on Opportunities in Science Meeting Nov 17-18, 1974 (1) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Draft Resolution; Appendix G for Agenda of Committee; 11/13/1974, Committee on Opportunities in Science Meeting Nov 17-18, 1974 (1) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Preliminary Agenda Meeting of the committee on Opportunities in Science; Washington, D. C.; 11/17-18/1974, Committee on Opportunities in Science Meeting Nov 17-18, 1974 (1); Handwritten Notes (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Report of a Conference on Career Education; AAAS and American School counselor Association; 1/27-28/1974, Committee on Opportunities in Science Meeting Nov 17-18, 1974 (1) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Article Physics Today "Need a Black Scientist with Doctoral Degree?"; Young, Herman A.; 11/1974, Committee on Opportunities in Science Meeting Nov 17-18, 1974 (1) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Report to Committee on Opportunities in Science; 3/01-11/01/1074, Committee on Opportunities in Science Meeting Nov 17-18, 1974 (1) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Agenda for Committee Meeting; 11/17-18/19; Brown, Janet W.; 11/06/1974, Committee on Opportunities in Science Meeting Nov 17-18, 1974 (1) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Nominations for Association Officers for 1976; Brown, Janet W.; 11/13/1974, Committee on Opportunities in Science Meeting Nov 17-18, 1974 (1) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Draft re: Science Education for Minorities and Women and the AAAS Role; (n. d.), Committee on Opportunities in Science Meeting Nov 17-18, 1974 (1) (Box 16, Folder 3)